Guide to the Eleze McKenzie collection of books in decorative binding sets.
McKenzie, Eleze collection of books in decorative binding
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Eleze McKenzie collection of books in decorative binding sets.
8045
Eleze. McKenzie
11 cubic feet
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Multi-volume sets in decorative bindings by standard authors.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Multi-volume sets in decorative bindings by standard authors.
SUBJECTS
Names:
McKenzie, Eleze.
Subjects:
Literature.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Novels of Jane Austen, London: Grant Richards, 1898 - ¾ blue calf, 1-10 (Box Reading Room)
- Bronte Novels, Edinburgh: John Grant, 1907- ¾ red calf, 1-11 (Box Reading Room)
- Dickens, 1-15 (Box 2)
- Complete Works of Robert Burn, London 1840 – green spine over blue calf boards, 1 (Box Reading Room)
- George Eliot, 1-3 (Box 2)
- George Eliot, 4-18 (Box 3)
- Emerson’s Journals, 1-4 (Box 3)
- Emerson’s Journals, 5-11 (Box 4)
- Emerson’s Works, 1-10 (Box 4)
- Emerson’s Works, 11-12 (Box 5)
- John Galsworthy, 1-6 (Box 5)
- Goldsmith Citizen of the World, II (Box 5)
- Hume History of England, 1-10 (Box 5)
- Smollett History of England, 1-2 (Box 5)
- Smollett History of England, 3-6 (Box 6)
- Johnson’s Lives of the Poets, 1-3 (Box 6)
- Ben Jonson’s Works, 1-9 (Box 6)
- Irving Sketch Book, 1 (Box 6)
- Lord Maculay, 1-5 (Box 6)
- Lord Maculay, 6-8 (Box 7)
- Charles Lamb, 1-12 (Box 7)
- Lane, 1-3 (Box 7)
- Works of Shakespeare.ed. George Long Duyckinck, Philadelphia: Porter & Coates, ½ calf spine gilt, 1-8 (Box Reading Room)
- Works of Shakespeare. Nonesvch Press, 1929, full calf, 1-7 (Box Reading Room)
- Works of William Makepeace Thackeray. London: Smith Elder, 1874, ¾ red morocco, gilt over marbled paper bds, T.E.G., 1-12 (Box Reading Room)
- Works of William Makepeace Thackeray. London: Smith Elder, 1874, ¾ red morocco, gilt, over marbled paper bds, T.E.G., 13-24 (Box Reading Room)
- Scotts Waverly Novels. Edinburgh: Adam & Charles Black, 1871, ¾ green morocco, gilt, over mpb., 1-18 (Box Reading Room)
- Scotts Waverly Novels. Edinburgh: Adam & Charles Black, 1871, ¾ green morocco, gilt, over mpb., 19-25 (Box Reading Room)